Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/courtneyshiau-boyd (LinkedIn) www.portillos.com/community (Company)

Top Skills

Project Coordination

Communication

Digital Project Management

Languages

Chinese (Elementary)
Mandarin Chinese (minimal)

Certifications

Al Studio Foundations Skill Badge Generative Al for Digital Marketers Al for Work Skill Badge Asana Foundations Skill Badge Workflow Specialist Certificate

Honors-Awards
President's List Honors

Courtney Boyd

Field Marketing Manager and Food Truck Project & Events Manager at Portillo's Hot Dogs

United States

Summary

Courtney is experienced in Promotions and Marketing with a demonstrated history of working in the entertainment and restaurant industries. Skilled in Partnership Marketing, Food Truck logistics planning, Event Management, Radio Promotions, and Media Relations. She is a strong marketing professional with a Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in Psychology from the University of South Florida.

Experience

Portillo's Hot Dogs 7 years 3 months

Field Marketing Manager December 2018 - Present (6 years 3 months) Greater Chicago Area

Field Marketing Coordinator December 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Florida & Indiana

Assist with the increase of same-store sales. Communicating and ensuring proper implementation and execution of marketing initiative objectives and results to restaurant management teams and Market Managers. Managing and organizing the day-to-day marketing needs for the Florida and Indiana Portillo's locations, including fundraising as well as community events and involvement. Maintain sponsor partnerships with organizations including the University of South Florida Athletics and the Tampa Bay Lightning (NHL) as well as the Indiana Pacers (NBA).

Beasley Media Group
Promotions Coordinator
July 2012 - December 2017 (5 years 6 months)
Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

As a Promotions Coordinator my job was to create a cohesive working environment for promotions, programming & sales. I ensured the client's

remotes and events were staffed and carried out successfully and that all parties were happy with the results. I coordinated the station staff for large station events such as WiLD Splash, Last Damn Show, Orlando's Holiday Toy Drive along with smaller scale events.

This role had me working closely with the Promotions Director, Account Executives and Clients to ensure that contests were executed in accordance with corporate compliance and FCC regulations to all parties satisfaction.

CBS Radio

Promotions Assistant

July 2011 - July 2012 (1 year 1 month)

Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

Set up for station remotes and events which included tents, games, sound systems and broadcasting equipment. Assisted in the office with administrative and clerical duties. Handled prizing and contest execution on-site at remotes and events.

Tween Brands

Lead Brand Representative

April 2010 - September 2011 (1 year 6 months)

Ensure guest satisfaction and empower young ladies to express their personalities through fashion!

Store supervisor/mamnager on-duty/keyholder. Achieved daily, weekly and monthly sales goals in addition to customer incentive program goals.

97.9 WRMF-FM (Palm Beach Broadcsting/Cobalt Broadcasting) Promotions Assistant

March 2007 - January 2010 (2 years 11 months)

West Palm Beach, Florida Area

WRMF street team.

Education

University of South Florida

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Psychology (2010 - 2011)

Palm Beach State College

Associate of Arts (A.A.), Psychology and Education (2007 - 2009)

G Star School of the Arts

H.S. Diploma, Film/Cinema/Video Studies · (2003 - 2007)